练习 7-11：搭建语调句。请跟读。
Exercise 7-11, Building an Intonation Sentence. Repeat after me.
think I bought a chicken salad sandwich.
Seven. I said I really think I bought a half a chicken salad sandwich.
Eight. I said I really think I bought a half a chicken salad sandwich this
afternoon.
Nine. I actually said I really think I bought a half a chicken salad sandwich
this afternoon.
Ten. I actually said, I really think I bought another half a chicken salad
sandwich this afternoon.
11. Can you believe I actually said, I really think I bought another half a
chicken salad sandwich this afternoon?
1. I did it. 2. I did it again. 3. I already did it again. 4. I think I already
did it again. 5. I said I think I already did it again. 6. I said I think I already
did it again yesterday.
7. I said I think I already did it again the day before yesterday.
1. I want a ball. 2. I want a large ball. 3. I want a large red ball. 4. I want a
large red bouncy ball. 5. I want a large red bouncy rubber ball. 6. I want a large
red bouncy rubber basketball.
1. I want a raise. 2. I want a big raise. 3. I want a big impressive raise. 4. I
want a big impressive annual raise. 5. I want a big impressive annual cost of
living raise.